Pedro Azevedo Minutentag

pedro.azvm@gmail.com 55 11 976593112 São Paulo - Brazil

Summary

Software developer focused on back-end development, both cloud and on-premise. Worked maintaining existing systems and developing new software.

Enjoys working with .NET technologies (.NET Framework / Core / ASP.NET / .NET 5).

Professional experience with other techonologies such as Java, C++, Python, NodeJs. Uses Angular for front-end development.

Comfortable designing and developing cloud based applications for the most part on azure.

Experience

Software Developer

Capgemini - RDI Software 04/2019 - Present

Currently working on the McDonalds account with multiple squads from different countries.

Worked on multiple projects:

- Supported legacy codebase (C++ / Java) and integrated it into current microservices architecture (.NET Framework).
- Created a cloud base applications on a microservice archtecture using ASP.NET Core
 and hosted it on azure. Worked on the design, application implementation and cloud
 environment.
- *Current*: Transformation project to migrate legacy components to new architecture using open source projects, .NET 5 and docker.

Jr. Software Developer

Jive Investments 01/2019 - 04/2019

Worked in an asset management firm, creating data mining process with **Python** and managing a **SQL Server** database. Introduced software development processes and helped design a **cloud** based architecture using AWS.

Game Developer

Bridge Games 07/2018 - 12/2018

Worked in a small startup developing games using **Unity3D**. Worked close to the users and wrote various **C**# tools.

Internship

В3

01/2016 - 07/2017

Worked in the department of credit analysis alongside statisticians and economists developing software for **data analysis**. Created systems using **R** and Shiny.

Links

- https://github.com/pedroaz
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/pedro-azevedo-627ab8b2/

Skills

- C#
- Azure

Angular

• Java

• C++

• Unity3D

• System Design

• Microservices

Education

Information Systems

USP • São Paulo, SP 12/2018

Physics (Interrupted)

USP • São Paulo, SP

Languages

• English

• Portuguese